

## **Shuai David Kong**

Operations Manager



## **Summary**

Operations professional with 6 years of experience and a proven track record, seeking to join an all-star team in the crypto industry. Proactive, broad-minded, and organized with a talent for unifying and motivating teams through coordination and authenticity. Crypto native.



## **Work History**

2015-08 - 2021-08

#### **Operations Manager**

TeamLogic IT, Mission Viejo CA

- -Managed the daily operations of a staff of 15 IT technicians, responsible for the functionality of over 3,000 endpoints across 130 small and medium-sized businesses.
- -Helped the company scale during a critical growth phase, and implemented procedures that coincided with annual recurring revenue more than doubling from \$1.8 to \$4.7 million in three years.
- -Worked closely with the VP and CEO to execute organizational plans, and provided regular status reports and updates to the entire staff by leading bi-weekly company meetings.
- -Managed physical asset allocations and associated costs by negotiating with clients, training technicians, and setting purchasing and invoicing standards.
- -Qualified and interviewed new hires; proactively hired based on the needs of the organization.
- -Trained junior-level employees and set objectives for performance and individual career growth.
- -Approved time off requests, addressed employee concerns, verified reimbursement claims for travel and equipment, and assisted with coordinating personnel between departments.

2021-08 - present

# Freelance Crypto Trader/Technical Strategy Consultant

Self employed, Various Locations

- -Provides technical consultations for Web 2.0 businesses and individuals interested in transitioning to web3, primarily focused on the data center space.
- -Advises on best practices for smart contract security, startup ecosystem landscape, NFT minting experiences, and bitcoin mining.
- -Trades crypto and NFTs based on fundamental and technical market analysis.



## **Personal Info**

#### **Emai**

sdavidkong@gmail.com

#### **Phone**

+30 698 828 0196

#### **Address**

5400 Fairway Dr. San Jose, CA



### **Skills**

- -Excellent written and verbal communication.
- -Deep knowledge of and experience working in crypto.
- -Multi-tasking, handling several deadlines in parallel and under time pressure.
- -Excellent interpersonal and collaboration skills.
- -Expertise in G-suite, Slack, and Microsoft Office.
- -Self-motivated and enthusiastic.
- -An understanding of MEV and the mission of Flashbots.
- -Consistently high level execution of tasks, with a hands on attitude.
- -Understands discretion and confidentiality.
- -Values humility, a supportive team player.



## Connect

Twitter:

@shuaidavidkong

ENS:

davidkong.eth

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/sdavidkong



## **Education**

2007-09 - 2011-05

**Economics and Sociology, Bachelor of Arts** 

University of California, Los Angeles